{
    "id": "275c612bca844dbc8e03c349b8e7e1d2",
    "title": "Articles Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Gold is ……………………….. precious metal.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9a042e4b170748f9b6d1b122ed2b526f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Honest men speak ……………………….. truth.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "76415f5398de486bb6b27528612bac8a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He looks as stupid as ……………………….. owl.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "78a6eb03b4df4a1e8f38d877e3948cc9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I would like to meet Brad Pit, …………………. actor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "75284d77312947a28f56036c10be70fb"
        },
        {
            "question": "What did you do with ……………………… camera I lent you?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "307504ce084b4dbeb4f658452a2e2cab"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is going out with ………………………… German girl.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "af17e825e985497eb350d380c82ff266"
        },
        {
            "question": "He remained ………………………… bachelor all his life.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "602aa44efcaa44928580abe367deeb8a"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘What is that noise?’ ‘I think it is ……………………….. helicopter.’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c35dc472b1194ea592c3e082000d21f1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I waited for ………………………….. hour and then I went home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "22fbcf04dfb14916814e5df5e4772ad0"
        },
        {
            "question": "She showed me …………………………. one-pound coin.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ef2494144a374c5799ab12eb854d99ed"
        }
    ]
}